http://www.trifibre.co.uk/privacy-policy

Shop by useAudio VisualLighting CasesPro Audio & Mixing Desk CasesProjector CasesRigging CasesTrussing CasesVideo Production CasesTelevision & Monitor CasesSpeaker CasesMusicGuitar CasesGuitar Amp CasesKeyboard CasesPedalboard CasesBand & OrchestraDrum & Sample Pad CasesCD Cases & Vinyl CasesPhotography & TechnologyDronesLaptop, Tablet, & Computer CasesPhotography & VideoRetail & ExhibitionGraphics DrumsGraphics Panel CasesPop Up Stand CasesPresentation Cases & BriefcasesViatori Portable Display ProductsToolsTool Boxes & CasesTool Trolleys & StoolsSportsArcheryCricketFishingGolfKit BoxesShootingRoad Trunks & StorageRack Flight CasesRack Case AccessoriesShop by brandTrifibreFlight CasesPlastic Transport BoxesDolly Boards & Case HardwareMoulded CasesMax CasesGeneral PurposeTool CasesPhotography & VideoMax Grip SeriesDrone CasesGun CasesMax Case AccessoriesSKB CasesGeneral PurposeDrone CasesPhotography & VideoRack SpacesSKB Music RangeSKB Sporting RangeChallenger CasesAluminium TrunksRack CasesGeneral PurposeTool Trolleys & StoolsChallenger Case AccessoriesPeli CasesPeli AirPeli MicroPeli MobilityPeli StormPeli ProtectorCamera CasesLaptop CasesTablet CasesPlastica PanaroAdvanced SeriesClassic SeriesK RangeProcase SeriesHardware CasesExcellent SeriesViatori Portable Display ProductsExplorer CasesShop by typeWaterproof CasesFlight CasesAluminium CasesPlastic CasesSoft Cases & Padded BagsClearance SaleCustom ServicesBespoke Flight CasesVacuum FormingPacking Crates & Custom Shipping ContainersPadded Bags & CoversPrinting and BrandingFoam Engineering & CNC RoutingRotational MouldingSync and ChargePoly CasesIndustriesAerospace & DefenceEmergency ServicesEngineeringEntertainment & AVExhibition & Trade ShowMascot CasesMedical & ScienceModel CasesMotorsportMusic, Gigs & BandsOil & GasPhoto BoothSales Rep Sample CasesSports & LeisureStorage & HandlingTesting & Measuring EquipmentFilm, Theatre, & Prop HireAbout TrifibreAbout TrifibreNews & InsightEnvironmental PolicyContact UsWhy Use a Flight Case? MenuPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Trifibre Ltd uses and protects any information
that you give Trifibre Ltd when you use this website.
Trifibre Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Any changes to our policy will be updated on this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.1.Pledge on PrivacyWe may collect information such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address that can be used to identify you. Trifibre Ltd will not process your personal data without your consent. In processing your personal data, we pledge to fully comply with internationally recognized standards of privacy protection. In so doing, we ensure compliance by our staff with strict standards of security and confidentiality.2.Intended Use of Personal DataMost of our services do not require any form of registration, allowing you to visit our site without telling us who you are. However, some services may require registration. When you register with us, you may need to complete certain fields (some are required and some are optional). In these situations, if you choose to withhold any personal data requested by us, it may not be possible for you to gain access to certain parts of the site and for us to respond to your query. Trifibre processes personal data for specific and limited purposes which we inform you about when we ask you for information. For example, we may collect and use personal data to provide you with information on products or services, to market products and services which we think may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you for other purposes such as market research. Information you send to Trifibre is used only to help resolve your problem and is otherwise kept private. Data sent to Trifibre is kept private and we only keep your data for as long as is reasonably needed for such purposes and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or documentation retention requirements. We may contact you via email, phone or mail.3.Non-Disclosure of InformationTrifibre will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your personal data to third parties outside the Trifibre group. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.4.How we use cookiesMost of the information that Trifibre collects from its website(s) is anonymous information, such as the pages you visit and searches you perform. When you visit our website we do not collect any personal data from you unless otherwise authorized by you. Anonymous information is processed by Trifibre to help improve the contents of the site and to compile aggregate statistics about individuals using our site for internal, market research purposes. In so doing, Trifibre may install “cookies” that collect the first level domain name of the user and the date and time of access. “Cookies” by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A “cookie” is a small piece of information which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Once the file is added the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a “cookie”, this will enable you to decide if you want to accept it or not. Rejecting a cookie may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.5.SpammingTrifibre does not condone “spamming”. Spamming is defined as sending unsolicited e-mails, usually of a commercial nature, in large numbers and repeatedly to individuals with whom the sender has had no previous contact or who have declined to receive such communications. In contrast, where Trifibre believes that certain product or other information is of importance to you it reserves the right to inform you by e-mail whilst giving you the choice of opting out of such service.6.Links to other WebsitesThis Privacy Policy applies only to Trifibre’s websites.  Our website may contain links to other websites which we believe may be of interest to our visitors. We do not have control over that website, we do however aim to ensure that such websites are of the highest standard. However, due to the nature of the World Wide Web, Trifibre cannot guarantee the standards of every website link it provides or be responsible for the contents of non- Trifibre sites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.7.Controlling your Personal InformationFrom May 25, 2018, GDPR will be enforced by data protection regulators across Europe. It will change how businesses can handle the information of their customers.At Trifibre we recognise the importance of protecting your personal information and are committed to processing it responsibly and in compliance with applicable data protection laws.Under GDPR you have the right to request your personal information Trifibre holds at any time, you also have the right to have your personal information deleted and restricted and ask for portability of your personal information. GDPR ensures that your information is gained ethically. To enforce this, when you provide us with your information (such as opting in) we will follow this up with an email asking you to opt in again, this process is referred to as double opt in. If you do not opt in again, we will assume you do not want us to hold your information and therefore your details will not be held on our data base. Under GDPR it is also important that you are able to opt out as easily as you are able to opt in and so there will be multiple links offered to you to make it easy for you to unsubscribe at any time if you wish to.If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at newsletter@trifibre.co.ukWe will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.As previously stated you may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data protection Act 2018. This service is free of charge and in accordance with GDPR we have to respond to your request no later than one month after receipt of correspondence. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email: info@trifibre.co.uk or telephone: 0116232316 or write to:Trifibre Ltd
17 Boston Road
Gorse Hill Industrial Estate
Leicester
LE4 1AW.List of cookies we collectThe table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store. COOKIE nameCOOKIE DescriptionCARTThe association with your shopping cart.CATEGORY_INFOStores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.COMPAREThe items that you have in the Compare Products list.CURRENCYYour preferred currencyCUSTOMERAn encrypted version of your customer id with the store.CUSTOMER_AUTHAn indicator if you are currently logged into the store.CUSTOMER_INFOAn encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDSStores the Customer Segment IDEXTERNAL_NO_CACHEA flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.FRONTENDYou sesssion ID on the server.GUEST-VIEWAllows guests to edit their orders.LAST_CATEGORYThe last category you visited.LAST_PRODUCTThe most recent product you have viewed.NEWMESSAGEIndicates whether a new message has been received.NO_CACHEIndicates whether it is allowed to use cache.PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CARTA link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.POLLThe ID of any polls you have recently voted in.POLLNInformation on what polls you have voted on.RECENTLYCOMPAREDThe items that you have recently compared.STFInformation on products you have emailed to friends.STOREThe store view or language you have selected.USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIEIndicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDSThe products that you have recently viewed.WISHLISTAn encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.WISHLIST_CNTThe number of items in your Wishlist.
Arrange a call back
Upload a specification
Copyright © 2020 Trifibre Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Company: 01890698 VAT: GB 395 5232 31. More information found in our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy.
Site by Alloneword.
